안녕
Hi!
Hey!
- 안녕
잠깐 인사하려고 들렀어
우리 지금 오하이오에 가봐야해
We're just here to say goodbye, we're off to Ohio.
Oh, right! Your adoption interview!
아, 입양 인터뷰하러 가는구나
우리 아기가 될지도 모르는 아이를
키우고 있는 여자를 만나러 가는거지
Yep, we're gonna meet the lady who could be carrying our baby.
믿을 수가 없어
I can't believe it. When you guys come back, you're gonna have a baby! That is so weird!
너희가 돌아올 때는
아이랑 같이 올거아냐
너무 이상해
그리고 사실이 아니지
And so incorrect!
그냥 임신 2개월쯤 된 여자야
She's only a couple of months pregnant. She liked our application but who knows if she's gonna like us.
우리 서류를 보고 좋아하긴 했지만
우릴 좋아할지는 알 수 없는 일이지
무슨 소리야
당연히 너희를 좋아할거야
Come on, she's gonna love you guys!
고맙긴한데, 너무
기대하지 않으려고 노력중이야
Uhm, thank you, but we're really trying not to get our hopes up.
잘 안될 가능성이 더 커
And a lot could still get in our way.
입양을 안하기로 결정할 수도 있고
다른 커플을 더 좋아할 수도 있는거잖아
Yeah. I mean, this girl could decide against adoption or she could like another couple better..
아기 이름은 뭘로 지을거야?
What are you gonna name the baby?
난 계속 주절주절 떠드는데
I can develop a condition in which I talk and talk and no one hears a word.
아무도 내 말은 안듣는군
생각해봐, 일이 잘돼서 그 여자가
너희들을 고를 수도 있잖아
But just think, ok? What if everything goes right? What if this woman does pick you guys?
세상에
Oh my God. She's gonna pick us!
우릴 고를거야
그러니까, 우린 기대 안하기로 한거지?
So we're standing firm on the 'not getting our hopes up'?
잘 안될 수 있다는건 알지만
You know, I know that things could still go wrong but if they don't? If this works out, we're gonna have a baby Chandler, a baby!
잘만 되면 우린
아기를 가지게 되는거야!
- 아기!
- 그렇...
Yes, but...
잘 될거야!
Oh my God, it's gonna WORK! We're gonna make it work! I'm gonna be a mommy and you're gonna be a daddy!
잘 되게 만들거야!
난 엄마가 되는거고
넌 아빠가 되는거야!
All right, I'll see you suckers. I'm gonna get me... A BABY!
가서 아이를 받아온 뒤에 보자구
알게 뭐야, 난 아빠가 될거야!
Ah, screw it, I'm gonna be a daddy!!
자막제작 - 코리아닷컴 프렌즈 동호회
(http://club.korea.com/friends)
FㆍRㆍIㆍEㆍNㆍDㆍS
1009. The One With The Birth Mother
한글번역
이상민(albireon@korea.com)
자막편집/싱크
남효주(hyojunet@nate.com)
자막에 대한 피드백은
동호회 게시판으로 해주십시요
피비랑 같이 있는 사람 누구야?
Hey, who's Phoebe with?
나랑 곧 섹스를 하게 될
사람이라고 말하고 싶군
I wanna say someone I'm gonna have sex with.
-Hey! -Hey!
So... who's your friend?
저 친구는 누구야?
Oh, that's Sarah.
아, 쟤는 사라야
안돼, 안돼!
꿈도 꾸지마, 알겠지?
No, no. Don't you get any ideas, ok? No, I'm not setting you up with any more of my friends!
난 이제 내 친구
너한테 소개 안시켜줄거야
왜?
OW, why, why, why?
왜냐하면 넌 한번
데이트하고 한번 자고
Because you'll date her once, sleep with her and then forget she exists!
그 사람이 있었다는
사실조차 잊어버리잖아
Oh, name one friend of yours that I did that with.
내가 그렇게 한 네 친구
이름 하나만 말해봐
- 맨디
- 맨디라구?
Mandy.
Mandy, huh? Uh... really hot blonde, big boobs?
정말 섹시한 금발에 가슴 컸던 애?
- 아니
- 어떻게 그런 여자를 잊을 수가 있겠어?
No.
I know why I don't remember her, huh?
내가 다른 사람이라고 생각하는거야?
Do you think I'm someone else?
내가 예전엔 네 친구들한테
좀 그랬을지도 모르지만
Ok. Look, I may not have treated your friends well in the past, but I have grown up a lot, really. Honest, Rach?
나 많이 성장했다고
진짜야, 정말이라고!
- 레이첼?
- 그렇기는 한 거 같아
Well, believe it or not, it's true. When Joey and I were together, he was wonderful. He was thoughtful and mature.
조이랑 잠깐 사귀는 동안...
정말 대단했어
사려깊고, 성숙하고...
And for the one week that we went out, he didn't sleep with anybody else!
우리가 사귀는 한 주 동안...
다른 여자랑 안잤다니까!
성장했지
Growth!
Fine, I'll give you her number.
알았어, 전화번호는 줄 게
그래, 고맙다
그리고 약속할 게
Ok, thank you. And I promise you I will not forget this one.
이번엔 절대 잊지 않을거야
- 맨디
- 사라!
Mandy.
SARAH!!
사라
Saraaah
- 안녕
-Hey! -Hi!
나, 패션에 대한 조언이 좀 필요한데...
Hey you guys, I need some fashion advice.
Oh!
이거 어때 보여?
How does this look?
너무 내렸어, 조금만 올려 봐
Well, it's a little low... pick it up a little...
조금만 더...
a little bit more... little bit more...
좀 더...
멋진데
There you go!
이제 던져버려
Now throw it away!
왜 그래, 이거 괜찮잖아
C'mon! This looks good!
로스, 내 말 들어
Ross, please, trust me. I buy 30 fashion magazines a month.
내가 한달에 패션잡지 30권은 사는데
Now, I don't know who's running for president or who that... NATO guy is, but...
누가 대통령 선거에 나오고
나토 사람 어쩌구 하는건 누군지 몰라도...
그 모자는 네 머리에서 될 수 있는 한
멀리 떨어뜨려 두는게 좋다는건 알아
I do know that you have to get as far away as you can from that hat.
젠장
Damn it! I have this date tomorrow night and I have to look cool!
내일 밤에 데이트가 있는데
멋져보이고 싶단 말야
패션에 대해서 조언이 필요하면
내일 레이첼이랑 같이 쇼핑가는데
Well, you know, if you want fashion help, Rachel and I are going shopping tomorrow.
같이 가면 되겠네
You're more than welcome to come with us, right?
그래? 잘됐다
나 뭔가 도움이 필요해
Really? That would be great. I mean, I have to do something, she kinda teased me about how I dress.
내가 옷입는 걸 가지고
자꾸 뭐라고 한단 말야
네 셔츠를 보면
왜 그러는지 알 수 있을거 같은데?
I can see why, nice shirt!
너도 똑같은거 입고 있잖아
You're wearing the same shirt.
망할 갭 매장은 왜이리 많은거야?
Stupid Gap on every corner!
편히 앉으시고요
금방 에리카와 같이 돌아오죠
Please, make yourselves comfortable and I will be back in a moment with Erica.
감사합니다
Ok, thank you
휴...
Uh, well this is it. Are you OK?
음, 여기까지 왔네
- 괜찮아?
- 응, 그냥 좀 이상해
Yeah. Just weird, you know. It's like: "Hi, I'm Chandler. May I have the human growing inside you?"
안녕하세요?
전 챈들러라는 사람인데
당신 안에 키우고 있는
인간을 데려가도 될까요?
Uh, you're gonna be great.
넌 잘 할 수 있을거야
넌 잘 할거야
YOU're gonna be great.
그건 당연하지
Well... obviously!
모니카, 챈들러
Monica, Chandler. I'd like you to meet Erica.
이쪽이 에리카에요
- 안녕하세요, 만나뵈서 반갑습니다
- 안녕하세요
Hi. It is so, so nice to meet you. Hi...
- 우리를 만나주셔서 감사합니다
- 안녕하세요
Thank you so much for agreeing to see us.
Hi.
- 잠시 얘기할 시간을 드리죠
- 알겠습니다, 감사합니다
I'll let you get acquainted. OK
모니카랑 챈들러죠?
So, it's Monica and Chandler? I only know you as file CRW33815-D.
CRW33815-D파일로만 알고 있어요
친구들은 우릴 그렇게 부르죠
That's what our friends call us.
정말 대단한 커플인것 같아요
Gosh, you know, you're just such an amazing couple. It's... kind of intimidating.
어떻게 보면 좀 무섭기도 하구요
그렇게 생각해 본 적은 없는데
I don't know about that.
정말요? 의사에다가...
You're kidding me? I mean, it's enough that you are a doctor.
목사 부인이시라니
But on top of it, you're married to a reverend?
- 제 생각에는 그게...
- 말하고 계시잖아요, 의사 선생님
I don't think that's exactly...
Let her finish, doctor.
- 안녕?
- 안녕
-Hey! -Hey
사라가 어제밤에
정말 즐거웠다고 하더라
Oh, my friend Sarah had a great time last night.
Yeah! So you're gonna call this one back?
이번엔 다시 전화할 거야?
No
아니
What are you talking about? Sarah's great!
무슨 소리 하는거야?
사라 정말 멋지잖아
정말? 네 그 멋진 친구가
무슨 짓을 했는지 알아?
Oh, really? You know what your great friend did?
저녁을 먹으러 갔는데
We're out to dinner, ok? We're getting along, having a really nice time.
같이 좋은 시간을 보내고 있었지
정말 멋진 여자라고 생각하고 있었어
I was thinking she was really cool. And then, out of nowhere...
근데 말이지
그게 다야?
That’s it? That’s why you won’t go out with her again? So, she took some fries, big deal!
그것 때문에 다시 안만나겠다는 거야?
감자 몇개 집어먹은게 무슨 큰 일이야?
Hey, hey, look! It’s not about a few fries... it’s about what the fries represent.
감자 몇조각이 문제가 아냐
그 감자 몇조각이
나타내는게 중요한거지
What?
- 그게 뭔데?
- 음식들 전부!
ALL FOOD!!
미안해, 너... 너한테
I’m sorry, I can’t believe I set you up with such a MONSTER!
너한테 그런
괴물을 소개시켜줘서
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Look. I take a girl out, she can order whatever she wants! The more, the better! All right?
여자랑 데이트 할 땐
여자가 뭘 시켜도 상관없어
많을 수록 좋아
다만, 가든 샐러드를 시켜놓고
내 것만 먹지 않으면 돼
Just don’t order a garden salad and then eat my food!
잘못하면 손가락을
잘릴 수도 있다고!
That's good way to lose some fingers!
Oh. Hi.
네가 와서 다행이다
Thank God you’re here. Listen to this!
- 이것 좀 들어 봐
- 뭐?
What?
어제밤에 조이랑
내 친구랑 저녁식사를 했는데
Joey and my friend were out last night and having dinner and she reaches over and takes a few of his fries...
조이 음식에서 감자 몇조각을 집어서
어머! 그럼 안되지
Oh! Oh, no!
뭐?!
What? You know about the, the, the plate thing?
그 접시 얘기를 아는거야?
그래, 알지
Oh, yeah, yeah. I know. Joey doesn’t share food.
조이는 절대 음식 안나눠 줘
I mean, just last week we were having breakfast and he had a couple of grapes on his plate...
바로 지난 주에
아침 먹고 있었는데
조이 접시에서 포도 몇알을 가져다가
너, 레이첼한테
포도도 안주는거야?
You wouldn’t let her have a grape?
아니, 내가 아니라...
Oh no! Not me! Emma!
에마 말야
JOEY DOESN’T SHARE FOOD!
조이는 음식을 절대 안나눠준다니까!
아무리 생각해 봐도
Well, I still think that it’s a stupid reason not to call someone again.
그건 내가 들어본 여자 차는
이유 중에 제일 바보같은 이유야
전화해, 알겠지?
You are calling her! OK? And if you need to, then just get an extra plate of fries for the table!
필요하면 여분으로
감자를 더 시키면 되잖아
I like that! A sharing buffer! Yeah! I’ll order some extra fries!
그거 좋은데
나눠먹을 여분을 두는거지
감자를 좀 더 주문해야겠네
양파링도 괜찮고
Maybe a plate of onion rings. Yeah.
칵테일 새우라던가
And some buffalo wings. Maybe individual pizza, huh? And some mozzarella sticks.
버팔로 윙..
조각피자..
모짜렐라 스틱도 괜찮겠다
우리가 무슨 얘기 하고 있었지?
What were we talking about?
여기 정말 멋진데!
This place is awesome!
여기선 아무 것도
못 찾을거 같아
You know, we should just go, I’m not gonna find anything here! This stuff is ridiculous!
이 옷들 다 이상해
Ah, this place is great!
여기 정말 너무 멋지잖아!
Wow!
레이첼 난 이런 건 안 입을거야
Rach, come on, I’m not gonna wear any of this!
Nothing silver. Ok? Nothing with hair! And nothing with padlocks on it!
은색
털 달린 옷
맹꽁이 자물쇠가 달린 옷도
로스, 이 중에 몇 개는
좀 많이 이상한건 알지만
Ross, look, I know that some of this stuff is out there, but I mean, come on, look at this, look at this sweater! I mean, this is just beautiful!
이거 봐
이 스웨터 좀 봐
정말 예쁘잖아
와우, 이건 정말 부드러운데
Wow, this is really soft.
350달러?
Three hundred and fifty dollars?
700달러에서 세일한 가격이네
200달러는 절약할 수 있네
Down from seven hundred, you are saving like two hundred bucks!
논리나 수학이나
요즘 위기를 맞고 있다지
Both logic and math are taking a serious hit today.
Hey, check this out! It’s totally you!
이거 봐
너한테 딱이다
- 와우
- 그래
Wow! Yeah!
이건 정말 괜찮은데?
Wow! Actually this looks pretty good! Yeah!
애들은 역시 애들이다
Boys will be boys?
왜? 맞는 말이잖아
What? They will be!
- 됐어, 나 그냥 갈래
- 안돼, 안돼
All right, that’s it, I’m getting out of here.
No, no, no! Ross, wait! Come on, alright! You know, there’s other stuff. Here’s a nice shirt, look at these nice pants...
로스, 가만 있어봐
여기 좋은 셔츠도 있고
이 바지도 있고
Huh, actually these might look pretty good on me.
이건 나한테 좀 어울릴 거 같은데
그래, 넌 그냥 가서 좀 걷다가 와
Yes, they will! You know what you should do? Just go take a walk, all right?
내가 네 사이즈 아니까
I know your size and I’m... I’m gonna pick up some really good stuff for you.
내가 괜찮은 옷들 좀 골라둘게
- 정말?
- 그래
Really?
Yes! And I know what looks sexy on guys. Please, just wear what I suggest, and she’s gonna go nuts for you.
난 어떤 옷이 섹시해
보이는지 안단 말야
내가 주는 옷을 입으면
그 여자는 너한테 푹 빠질거야
그러니까 네 말은...
So, you’re saying, uh, if I wear these pants I might be getting into hers?
그러니까 이걸 입으면
그 여자랑 잘해볼 수 있다는거지?
왜 남자들은 항상 나한테
저런식으로 얘기하는거야?
Why do men keep talking to me like this?
제가 의사고 아내가
목사라는게 중요한가요?
So, the fact that I am a doctor, and my wife’s a reverend, that’s important to you?
다른 서류들도 많이 봤지만
Yeah, I read some great applications, but then I thought “who better then a minister to raise a child!”
누가 목사님보다
아이를 잘 키우겠어요?
아멘
Amen.
그리고 의사 아버지랑 같이
있으면 아이도 잘 돌봐주실거고
Plus I thought the baby would be in good hands with a doctor!
Uh, good hands. Healing hands.
오, 좋은 손이죠
치료의 손
목사님, 하나만 물어볼게요
Reverend, can I ask? Does the bible say anything about adoption?
성서에 입양에 대한 말이 있나요?
"그리하라"라고 나와있죠
It says “Do it!"
그리고 "보라, 그녀는 그들에게
아이를 입양시켰고"
And behold she did adopt onto them a baby.
"그 결과는 좋았노라"
And it was good.
- 와우
- 네
Wow.
Yeah, wow.
와우!
두분 다 그런 직업을 가지고
있다는걸 믿을 수가 없어요
I was wondering you both have such serious jobs. Would you have time to take care of a baby and your flock?
아이도 돌보면서 신도들까지
신경쓰실 수 있겠어요?
우리 신도들은
스스로 알아서 잘 하죠
Oh, no, no, my flock, my flock is good, I mean, yeah, my flock pretty much takes care of themselves by this point.
좋은 신도죠
Good flock. Flock, flock, flock.
의사라면 일하는
시간도 많으실텐데
Being a doctor that must take up a lot of time.
No-ot for me it doesn’t.
저한테는 안맞는 말이에요
자, 어떻게 되가나요?
So, how’s everything going in here?
좋아요, 물어보고
싶은건 다 물어봤어요
We’re great, I think I may have asked all my questions.
Do you have any question for Erica?
에리카한테 뭐
묻고 싶은건 없으세요?
네, 있어요
Yeah, actually. So, you read a file that you liked and you gave the agency the serial number and they contacted us?
그러니까 서류를 보고나서
맘에 드는 사람의 시리얼번호를 주고
에이전시가 우리에게 연락한거죠?
그럼요, 우리 시스템은
정말 믿을 만 하죠
Yes, our system insures total anonimity. We’re very proud of it.
- 저희도 자랑스럽답니다
- 그래야죠
You should be. You’re really on top of stuff.
일처리 정말 잘하시네요
Well, then if there’s nothing else, then the two of us should talk.
그럼, 더 나눌 말씀은 없는거죠?
네
Actually, I don’t think we have to.
다른 말은 더 안해도 될 거 같아요
안해도 된다구요?
We don’t?
네, 서류를 읽어보고 이 사람들이라면
됐다고 거의 확신했어요
Yeah, when I read about you two, I was pretty sure I wanted you, but I just thought we should meet face to face.
그냥 한번 어떤 사람들인지
보고 싶었어요
결정했어요
I've made my decision. I choose them.
이 분들로 할래요
세상에, 너무 기뻐요
Oh my God, this is great! This is so great! Did you hear that?
정말 좋다, 자기도 들었어?
그래, 나도 들었어
Yeah, I did.
고마워요
Hey, thank you. Thank you so much.
너무 고마워요
당신은 꼭 천국에 갈 거에요
You are SO going to Heaven!
We got some really great stuff!
- 힘들었지?
- 그래
Yeah, yeah but I am not sure about some of the bra's I got.
내가 산 브라들이 다 괜찮은지
잘 모르겠어
그래? 몇개 입고 보여줄래?
Oh! Really? Do you wanna try some of them on for me?
아, 그래
Oh! okay. Wait, are we in Joey's imagination?
잠깐, 우리 이거 혹시
조이의 상상속에 있는거야?
이런, 실수로 로스 쇼핑백을
하나 가져왔네
Oh, no! I took one of Ross' bags by mistake, and one of mine is missing.
그리고 내꺼 하나가 안보여
oh, well, Ross probably has it, you can get it from him later.
아마 로스가 가지고 있겠지
나중에 받아
봐봐
So? What do you think?
어떻게 생각해?
이젠 같은 셔츠 입을 일은 없겠네
I think we're not wearing the same shirt anymore!
그래, 그래
레이첼이 골라준 옷이야
Yeah! Yeah! Rachel picked it out for me. She told me to trust her and you know what?I'm glad I did!
자길 믿으라고 그랬어
믿기를 잘한거 같아
오는 길에 다른 사람들이
다들 쳐다보더라고
I turned quite a few heads on my way over here.
아무리 생각해도
그거 안입는게 좋을거 같다
Dude, I really don't think you should be wearing that.
알았다
Oh, I see, somebody is afraid of a little competition with the ladies?
누군가가 여자를 두고 경쟁할 사람이
생길까봐 겁나나보지?
누군가가 여자나 보군
Looks like someone IS the ladies!!
넌 네가 이런 옷을
소화할 수 없으니까 질투하는거야
You're just jealous because you couldn't pull this off. Yeah, now if you'll excuse me, I have a date.
난 데이트가 있어서 가봐야겠다
See? ALL eyes on ME!
봐, 다들 날 보잖아!
우린 거기 서명하면 안돼
We are NOT signing those papers.
왜 안돼?
Why not?
It's wrong. They made a mistake. They think we're somebody else.
잘못된거잖아
그 사람들이 실수해서
우릴 다른 사람으로 착각하고 있잖아
신은 신비한 방법으로 일을 하셔
God works in mysterious ways.
그만 안 할래?
You have gotta stop!
에리카는 우릴 좋아했어
But she liked us.
에리카는 의사 챈들러랑
목사 모니카를 좋아한거지
She likes Doctor Chandler and Reverend Monica.
Well, if you think about it, I am kind of like a Reverend.
생각해봐
난 목사랑 비슷해
I mean, as a chef, I serve God, by feeding the hungry and poor.
난 요리사로써 굶주린 사람들에게
먹을 것을 줘서 신의 뜻을 실천하잖아
음식 값이 34달러 95센트야
Your Veal Chop is $34.95!
챈들러, 우린 기회를 얻은거야
Chandler, I think we have been given an opportunity.
실수는 이미 지나간거고
지금 서류를 쓰고 있잖아
I mean, the mistake has already been made. They are writing up the paper right now.
우린 에리카가 고른 사람들이 아냐
But we are not the one she chose! How can you feel okay about this?
어떻게 그걸 알면서도 괜찮은거야?
왜냐하면...
Because... We may not be who she thinks we are but no-one will ever love that baby more than us.
우린 에리카가 생각하는
사람은 아닐지 몰라도
우리보다 저 아기를
더 사랑하는 사람은 없어
알아
I know.
다음에 또 누가 우리한테 아이를 준다고
할 때까지 얼마가 걸릴지 어떻게 알아?
I mean, who knows how long it's gonna take for someone else to give us a baby? What if, what if no one ever picks us?
아무도 우릴 안고르면 어떻게 해?
Oh, honey...
제발
Please.. please, we are so close.
우린 지금 거의 다 왔어
모니카, 나도 아이를 원해
Monica, I want a baby too, but this woman is giving away her child. She deserves to know who it's going to.
하지만 저 여자는 자기 아이를
다른 사람들에게 보내는거야
그 사람들이 누군지는 알아야 한다고
그래, 맞아
Okay, right.
So, we'll tell the truth and who knows, you know, maybe she'll like us for us.
어쩌면, 사실을 얘기해도
우리를 좋아할 지도 모르잖아
Maybe she will. Uh! Why couldn't I have been a Reverend?
아마 그럴거야
목사가 됐어야 하는데
너 유태인이잖아
You're Jewish!
겉만 그렇지
Technicality!
여자분은 가든 샐러드
A garden salad for the lady
맛있어 보이네요, 잘 시켰어요
Oh, that looks great! Good ordering!
Seafood platter for the gentleman and extra fries. Enjoy!
해산물 요리는 남자분
그리고 감자 추가
즐거운 시간 되세요
Mmmh, those fries look delicious.
감자가 아주 맛있어보이네요
감자 튀김을 좋아하는줄 몰랐네요?
Oh, I didn't know you liked French fries. Help yourself! What's mine is yours.
마음껏 드세요
제껀 다 당신꺼에요
Oh wow, are those stuffed clams?
우와, 그거 속 채운 대합이에요?
Uuuh.. yes, they are my stuffed clams.
네, 제가 시킨 속 채운 대합이에요
감자튀김 좀 더 드시는게 어때요?
How about those fries though, huh?
맛있더라구요
They are delicious.
당신은 너무 아름다워요
그거 알아요?
You are beautiful, you know that?
너무 고마워요
That is so sweet..
okay...
뭐하는 짓이에요?
NOW look what you did!!
What? what is the matter with you?
도대체 왜 그래요?
전 다른 사람이 내 접시에서
음식을 가져가는걸 싫어해요
I don't like it when people take food off of my plate, okay?
방금 당신껀 다 제꺼라고 했잖아요
But you just said "What's mine is yours"?
진심이 아니었다고요
WELL, I DIDN'T MEAN IT!
알았어요
Fine, I'm sorry, I didn't think it was that big a deal.
미안해요, 그게 그렇게
대단한 일인지 몰랐어요
미안해요, 제가
너무 과민반응을 했네요
I'm sorry, I'm overreacting. Okay, It's just when it comes to food, I have certain rules.
음식에 대해서는...
저만의 룰이 있거든요
Ok,I mean there are things you do..and you know, things.. that you don't do
해도 되는 일이 있고
해선 안되는 일이 있다는거죠
Wow, this place looks great.
여기 멋진데요
Oh! You are gonna love it! and I'm so glad, we're finally doing this.
정말 좋아할 거에요
저도 여기 오게되서 정말 기뻐요
저도요
Me too!
Here..
오늘 즐거웠어요
So this was fun!
아까 일은 정말 미안해요
I really am sorry about, you know..before. I just want to make sure you know that I really do like you.
하지만 내가 당신을 정말
좋아한다는 건 알아주셨으면 해요
대합만큼은 아니죠
Sure. Just not as much as clams.
속을 채운 대합이었잖아요
Well, stuffed clams.
여자분은 초콜렛 토르트
Chocolate Torte for the lady, cheesecake for the gentleman.
남자분은 치즈케익
죄송한데요
Uh, excuse me sir, there seems to be some sort of red crap on my cheesecake.
치즈 케익 위에 빨간 쓰레기 같은게
올라와 있는데
Yes, that's Raspberry coule.
그건 라즈베리 쿨리입니다
So stupid, ordering cheesecake, trying to be healthy.
무슨 이런 치즈케익이 다 있어
"건강을 지키세요!"
Oh my God! Mmmm!
Oh, all right, I'll just have what she's having instead.
이거 말고 저 분하고
같은 걸로 갖다 주세요
죄송하지만
저게 마지막 조각이었습니다
Oh, I'm sorry sir, that was our last piece.
Mmmm! Mmm!
Oh, no! This is work. I should call in. Can you excuse me?
일이에요, 잠시 전화 좀
하고 와도 괜찮겠죠?
그럼요, 괜찮아요
Oh yeah, sure. No problem.
뭐하는거에요?
What are you doing? I thought you don't share food.
음식은 안 나눠먹는다면서요?
안나눠먹긴요
Sure I do.
쿨리 먹을래요?
Coule?
No. If I can't have your clams, you can't have my dessert. This is a two way street.
내가 당신 대합을 먹을 수 있었다면
당신도 내 디저트를 먹을 수 있었겠죠
이건 일방통행이 아니라고요
정말요?
Really?
그럼요
Really! Now this all better be here when I come back.
제가 돌아왔을 때
다 남아있어야 할거에요
그럼요, 그 정도는 제어할 수 있다구요
Yeah, of course. I can control myself.
그만 쳐다 봐
Stop staring at me!
그냥 쪼끔만 먹는건데 어때?
Why, just a tiny little...
Oh-oh!
미안하지도 않네요
I'm not even sorry.
-Hi. -Hey -Hey
이게 입양을 위해
작성해야 할 서류들이구요
So, these are the preliminary forms for an open adoption. There's a lot to go over, but I'll explain everything as we go through it.
해야 할 일들이 많지만
제가 다 설명해 드릴게요
I-Is... Is that a picture?
저게 사진인가요?
네, 지난 주에 찍은
초음파 사진이에요
Yeah. It's a sonogram they took of the baby last week. I thought you might want to see it.
보고싶어하실 것 같아서요
의사 선생님, 이것 좀 봐요
Look, doctor!
서명을 하기 전에
Look, before we sign anything we really have to talk...
얘기를 좀 해야할것 같은데요
우리는 당신이
생각하는 사람이 아니에요
We're not who you think we are.
무슨 말씀이시죠?
I don't understand.
에이전시에서
무슨 잘못이 있었나봐요
The agency must have made some mistake. My wife is not a reverend and I'm not a doctor.
제 아내는 목사가 아니고
저도 의사가 아니에요
뭐라고요?
What? That's impossible.
있을 수 없는 일이에요
원하신다면, 당신을 수술해서
증명해 드릴 수도 있어요
I could perform an operation on you and prove it if you'd like.
잠시만요, 서류를 좀
확인해보고 올게요
I'll go check your file. Excuse me.
그럼, 당신들은 누구에요?
So who are you?
우린 진짜로 모니카와 챈들러고
뉴욕에서 왔어요
Well, our names really are Monica and Chandler. We're from New York.
하지만 중요한 건...
Yeah, but the important thing to know about us, is how much we would care for this little baby.
우리가 얼마나
이 아기를 사랑하는 지에요
그럼, 아까는 저한테
거짓말 하신 거에요?
So you lied to me before?
Well, we... "bore false witness"...
"거짓 증언 하지 않았어요"
See? I could be a reverend.
당신의 목사는 될 수 있어요
믿을 수가 없어요
I can't believe this.
우린 사실을 말한 뒤에도
우리를 한번 고려해...
But we were hoping that since we told you the truth that you still might consider...
아이를 당신들한테 주는 걸요?
Giving you my baby? You think I'd give you my child after this?
이러고 난 뒤에도
아기를 줄 거라고 생각했어요?
바로 결정을 하라는게 아니고요
적어도 우리 서류를 보고...
Well, you don't have to decide right now, but if you could just look at our file...
서류를 보고 싶지도 않아요
I don't want to look at your file! This is over.
끝이에요!
잠깐만 기다려봐요
Erica. Wait!
당신한테 할 말 없어요
I've nothing to say to you.
화내는게 당연하죠
You have every reason to be upset. We did lie.
우리가 거짓말을 했어요
하지만 그건 우리가 아이를 가지려고 너무
오랫동안 기다리고 노력해왔기 때문이에요
But only because we've been waiting and trying to have a baby for so long.
다음에 다시 기회가 올 때까지
얼마나 걸릴지도 알 수 없어요
And we don't know how long it's gonna be before we get another chance again.
목사님께 기도나
해달라고 하지 그래요?
Why don't you ask the reverend to pray on it?
에리카, 제발요
Erica, please. Just consider us.
그냥 우리를 고려만 해봐요
에이전시에 우리
서류를 보여달라고 해보세요
Ask them to see our file. Our last name's Bing. My wife's a chef and I'm in advertising.
성은 빙이고
아내는 요리사에, 전 광고일을 해요
그래요
Oh yeah. I actually liked you guys. But it doesn't matter, because what you did was wrong.
사실 당신들이 좋은
사람이라고 생각은 해요
하지만 당신들이 잘못한 거에요
하지만 우릴 좋아했잖아요
But you did like us. And you should.
그리고 그래야해요
아내는 대단한 사람이에요
My wife's an incredible woman.
사랑할줄 알고, 헌신하고, 아끼고
She's loving and devoted and caring.
그리고 이 말은 저사람한테 하지 말아요
저 여자는 항상 옳아요
And don't tell her I said this but the woman's always right...
I love my wife more than anything in this world.
전 이 세상 무엇보다 아내를 사랑해요
And I... It kills me that I can't give her a baby...
내가 아내에게 아기를 안겨줄 수
없다는 게 죽을만큼 힘들어요
저도 정말 아기를 원해요
I really want a kid.
아기를 갖게 된다면
전 좋은 아빠가 되는 법을 배우겠죠
And when that day finally comes, I'll learn how to be a good dad.
하지만 내 아내는...
But my wife... she's already there. She's a mother... without a baby...
벌써 그래요
좋은 엄마라고요
아기는 없지만...
제발요
Please?
아직도 저 아기를 원해?
You still want that baby?
챈들러 빙, 그대에게
신의 가호가 함께하기를
God bless you Chandler Bing!
자막제작 - 코리아닷컴 프렌즈 동호회
(http://club.korea.com/friends)
알고 보니, 이거 여성용 스웨터였어
Turns out this sweater is made for a woman.
So, why are you still wearing it?
근데 왜 아직도 입고 있어?
부드럽거든
Because it's soft...
넌 어땠어?
Hey, so how was your date?
Ooh... Not so good.
별로였어
Well, looks like it's just the two of us tonight, huh old buddy?
오늘 밤은 우리 둘 뿐인거 같네
그래, 그리고 말야
Yeah, and you know what? We could do a lot worse.
우리가 할일은 많아
조이는 음식을 나눠먹지 않아!
JOEY DOESN'T SHARE FOOD!